Extraordinary civilian death toll that has happened as a result of this war.
Do you believe that anything that Israel has done in these six weeks of fighting has amounted to a war crime?
Of course not. Of course not.
And it's like, let's not forget what Hamas started.
They broke the first ceasefire.
So, you know, this is what happens when we have so many public servants, you know, politicians, officials, even people that are in appointed positions who are simply just not educated about things that are going on around the world.
And we know that this is a real thing because these are Americans.
And in America, there simply isn't a built in concept of global consciousness.
There are so many people within our State Department, and this is going to maybe shock you, that did not know about Israel and Palestine until October 7th.
Yeah, I know people and they've told me.
So when we see this, we know that this is someone who's speaking from literally someone speaking to them and them just running it off.
So John Ferdinand and his hoodie turned out to be quite the disappointment.
So he's just another example of who you're going to not give your vote to if you are standing for people who are actually standing for people.